xeikon.com 2013-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Xeikon N.V.

##  Xeikon Privacy Policy

Updated: March 2013

###  Introduction

At Xeikon, we are committed to protecting and respecting your personal data. Based on policies and regulations unique to the European Union (amongst others directives 95/46 and 2002/58), we have set forth below our privacy terms with regard to our websites, explaining how we use personal data collected from you on our websites. These include:

We invite you to carefully read this policy to understand our data-processing practices.   

For the purpose of the applicable national and EU-legislation, the data controller for personal data collected on our websites is Xeikon NV., Brieversstraat 70, 4529 GZ Eede The Netherlands (hereinafter referred to as “Xeikon” or “we”).

We may modify this Policy from time to time, for example to comply with future legislation, or to deal with future developments. Therefore, please check this Policy periodically for changes, in particular when you submit personal data on our websites. Any personal data collected about EU visitors via our websites, or when you contact Xeikon’s sales, customers, or technical support via these websites, can be processed outside the European Union too. When you provide such personal data to Xeikon, you consent to the processing of your data in countries outside the European Union in which our website may also be operated.

This Policy only applies to the processing of personal data collected by us on our websites. Our other data-processing activities are covered by other Xeikon policies.  

###  Purposes

We process personal data collected on our websites for the following purposes (hereinafter referred to as “Xeikon Purposes”): 

  * Xeikon/basysPrint/ThermoFlexX governance;
  * The provision of Xeikon/basysPrint/ThermoFlexX services and products;
  * Newsletter and other customer communications;
  * Organization of events;
  * The operation of our websites (IP addresses, cookies, web acceleration, and so on)

More information about the use of your data for these and other purposes is given below. 

###  Events

When you register for events, we collect personal data related to your participation to the event. 

We process your data for purposes relating to event registration, administration, security management, accounting, records keeping, to offer event-related products and services, and for conducting satisfaction surveys. 

The list of participants is sent in advance of the event to the exhibiting companies to allow them to present their products and services directly to you, and may be used by us for our own advertising and marketing purposes. You may opt out of this list in the online registration form.

###  Newsletters and Other Customer Communications

We may use personal data that we collect on our websites to provide you with newsletters and to invite you to participate in customer consultations and satisfaction surveys. 

We only send you newsletters, customer consultations, or satisfaction surveys that relate to Xeikon/basysPrint services and products. 

In each mailing, we remind you about your right to opt out of our newsletters, customer consultations, or satisfaction surveys mailing lists. 

You may opt out or unsubscribe from the above mailings at any time by sending an email to the designated email address.

Some of these newsletters and communications are sent to you on our behalf by suppliers specialized in mass mailings. We request those suppliers to provide us with the appropriate data-protection and data-security commitments (see ‘Sharing Data’ section below). 

###  Operation of our Websites

####  General 

Xeikon or its service providers may gather information regarding to your activities, preferences and transactional data relating to your use of our websites. We collect and use, and may form time-to-time supply third parties with, information as anonymous, collected or aggregated user data for the purposes of analysis, quality control and improvements to our websites.

####  IP Addresses

When you browse our websites, you do so anonymously. For our internal purposes, we may use IP addresses (the internet address of your computer) stored in web logs to generate aggregate statistics on surf behavior, such as traffic patterns and time spent on a page.

####  Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive or in your browser memory. We may use cookies for authentication purposes, to track user sessions, to repopulate fields, or to track online acceptance or language preference.

The information stored with cookies may include your name, first name, registration number, language preference, login ID, and IP addresses. 

Other sites accessed through your use of our websites may use cookies that remain on your browser after you visit the site. Therefore, please consult the privacy policies of any sites that you access through our websites. You may also wish to: (i) set your browser to notify you when such cookies have been placed on your browser, and/or (ii) examine your browser to disable or remove such cookies. However, please note that disabling or removing certain cookies can interfere with the functionality or potentially desirable features of certain sites, such as automatic log on capabilities or site-visit recommendations based on identification of return visits.

####  Web Acceleration Services 

For purposes of accelerating the consultation of our websites, we use the services of a supplier specialized in web-acceleration services. This requires caching the content of our websites on a substantial number of servers worldwide. 

This supplier only processes data on our instructions, provides sufficient guarantees in respect of technical and organizational data security measures, and has committed to notify us in case of a security breach compromising your personal data (see also ‘Sharing Data’ section below). 

####  Data Security

We are committed to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, alteration, and unauthorized disclosure or access. 

Please be aware that we cannot ensure the security of your data on your computer or during transmission over the internet. In this regard, we advise you to take every possible precaution to protect personal data stored on your computer and transiting on the Internet. 

####  Data Submitted on Behalf of Someone Else

When you provide us with personal data relating to someone else, be sure to collect and supply such personal data in accordance with local applicable law. 

For example, you may have to inform that other person about parts of this Statement in order to comply with local applicable law. 

###  Your Rights

With regard to personal data collected on our websites, you may use the email addresses provided in this Statement to: 

  * exercise your access and correction rights, and request deletion;
  * submit inquiries or other communications regarding Xeikon’s privacy policies;
  * object to or restrict Xeikon’s use of your information for direct-marketing purposes.

We will handle all requests with care and diligence, and take corrective actions in accordance with both national and EU legislation. 

###  Privacy Officer

The Xeikon Privacy Officer carries out internal supervision in connection with our responsibilities under this Statement. 

You may exercise your rights and address any questions to the Privacy Officer: 

  * by letter to Xeikon NV., attention of Privacy Officer, Brieversstraat 70, 4529 GZ Eede, The Netherlands;
  * by email to [privacy.officer@xeikon.com](mailto:privacy.officer@xeikon.com).

###  Sharing Data

We will not allow third parties to use your personal data for their own purposes without your consent. 

When required for the Xeikon Purposes, we may share your data with other offices in the Xeikon group, carefully selected suppliers, or other selected third parties (typically Xeikon/basysPrint partners or subcontractors). 

Before sharing your data, we require such third parties to only process your personal data on our instructions and to provide sufficient guarantees in respect of the technical and organizational security measures protecting the data-processing activities. 

Such Xeikon/basysPrint offices or third parties may be located in or outside the European Economic Area (EEA), including in countries that do not offer a level of data protection considered as adequate under EU member state legislation. 

In the latter case, we ensure the lawfulness of such transfers by: 

  * agreeing with other Xeikon/BasysPrint offices on the standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission Decision 2004/915/EC of 27 December 2004; 
  * agreeing with third parties on the most appropriate statutory, contractual, or self-regulatory basis (for example adherence to the “Safe Harbor Principles) to allow such transfers.
